https://anin.com.na/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHome >> Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://anin.com.na.The website anin.com.na sells Textile products handmade in Namibia. We offer Natural materials like cottons and linen. The Threads used for embroidery mostly consists of colourfast materials to protect the textiles from colour damage. Due to the nature of textiles, quality and colours might vary slightly. Authenticity of hand embroidered products will therefore reveal slight differences from website due but not limited toColours display differently on different computer monitors/ smartphones/ tablets etc. we are unable to guarantee perfect colour accuracyhand embroidered motifs are left up to the interpretation of the individual embroiderer and will therefore be uniquely different on every product.Please do not use, download or distribute any content on this website without the consent of the Company Owners. All visual, audio and design material on this Website is protected by Namibian and International Copyright Laws.The supplier of the goods on this E-Commerce site, www.anin.com.na, is Anin Embroidery CC at registered office 78 Sam Nujoma drive, Klein Windhoek, Windhoek, Namibia. Our Postal address is Private Bag 13094 Windhoek, Namibia. What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsNo Information from contact forms are used for any marketing purposes. The information you supply would be your name and email adress which we will utilise to comunicate with you.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWe use Google analytics and therefore have included pixels on some of the pages to monitor use and improve your experience while browsing the page.Who we share your data withYour Data is not Shared with any third party.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationYour information remains private and is not shared.Additional informationHow we protect your dataYour data is kept on our Website server and covered by the same security measures that we cover our website with.What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataWe might use simple information like Sex age and demographics if you supply it to better direct newsletters etc.Source: WoocommerceWe collect information about you during the checkout process on our store.What we collect and storeWhile you visit our site, we’ll track:Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewedLocation, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shippingShipping address: we’ll ask you to enter this so we can, for instance, estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order!We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:Send you information about your account and orderRespond to your requests, including refunds and complaintsProcess payments and prevent fraudSet up your account for our storeComply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxesImprove our store offeringsSend you marketing messages, if you choose to receive themIf you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. For example, we will store order information for XXX years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email address and billing and shipping addresses.We will also store comments or reviews, if you choose to leave them.Who on our team has accessMembers of our team have access to the information you provide us. For example, both Administrators and Shop Managers can access:Order information like what was purchased, when it was purchased and where it should be sent, andCustomer information like your name, email address, and billing and shipping information.Our team members have access to this information to help fulfill orders, process refunds and support you.What we share with othersWe share information with third parties who help us provide our orders and store services to you; for example —PaymentsWe accept payments through VCS. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to VCS, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information.Please see the VCS Privacy policy for more details.Source: Really simple SSLReally Simple SSL and Really Simple SSL add-ons do not process any personal identifiable information, so the GDPR does not apply to these plugins or usage of these plugins on your website. You can find our privacy policy here.Source: MailChimp for WooCommerceWhen shopping, we keep a record of your email and the cart contents for up to 30 days on our server. This record is kept to repopulate the contents of your cart if you switch devices or needed to come back another day. Read our privacy policy here.Source: AkismetWe collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).
